[
  {
    "question": "How many goals have occurred so far in the first half up to the 29:43 mark?",
    "choices": [
      "A. 0",
      "B. 1",
      "C. 2",
      "D. 3"
    ],
    "answer": "B",
    "type": "past",
    "question_level": "match",
    "related_event_index": [
      2
    ],
    "current_event_index": 2,
    "index": 0,
    "event_type": "goal"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which team has scored more goals in the first half up to the 29:43 mark?",
    "choices": [
      "A. Liverpool",
      "B. Opponent",
      "C. Both teams have scored equally",
      "D. No goals yet"
    ],
    "answer": "A",
    "type": "past",
    "question_level": "team",
    "related_event_index": [
      2
    ],
    "current_event_index": 2,
    "index": 1,
    "event_type": "goal"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who was the first player to score in the match up to the 29:43 mark?",
    "choices": [
      "A. Philippe Coutinho",
      "B. Emre Can",
      "C. Roberto Firmino",
      "D. No goals yet"
    ],
    "answer": "B",
    "type": "past",
    "question_level": "player",
    "related_event_index": [
      2
    ],
    "current_event_index": 2,
    "index": 2,
    "event_type": "goal"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many total goals occurred in the first half?",
    "choices": [
      "A. 1",
      "B. 2",
      "C. 3",
      "D. 4"
    ],
    "answer": "B",
    "type": "half",
    "question_level": "match",
    "related_event_index": [
      2,
      3
    ],
    "current_event_index": null,
    "index": 3,
    "event_type": "goal"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which team had the most goals in the first half?",
    "choices": [
      "A. Liverpool",
      "B. Opponent",
      "C. Both teams have scored equally",
      "D. No goals"
    ],
    "answer": "A",
    "type": "half",
    "question_level": "team",
    "related_event_index": [
      2,
      3
    ],
    "current_event_index": null,
    "index": 4,
    "event_type": "goal"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which player was involved in the most goals in the first half?",
    "choices": [
      "A. Emre Can",
      "B. Roberto Firmino",
      "C. Philippe Coutinho",
      "D. No players"
    ],
    "answer": "C",
    "type": "half",
    "question_level": "player",
    "related_event_index": [
      2,
      3
    ],
    "current_event_index": null,
    "index": 5,
    "event_type": "goal"
  },
  {
    "question": "Will there be more goals in the first half after the 29:43 mark?",
    "choices": [
      "A. Yes",
      "B. No",
      "C. Only one more",
      "D. Two more"
    ],
    "answer": "A",
    "type": "future",
    "question_level": "match",
    "related_event_index": [
      3
    ],
    "current_event_index": 2,
    "index": 6,
    "event_type": "goal"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which team is more likely to get the next goal after the 29:43 mark?",
    "choices": [
      "A. Liverpool",
      "B. Opponent",
      "C. Both teams",
      "D. No more goals"
    ],
    "answer": "A",
    "type": "future",
    "question_level": "team",
    "related_event_index": [
      3
    ],
    "current_event_index": 2,
    "index": 7,
    "event_type": "goal"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which player is most likely to be involved in the next goal after the 29:43 mark?",
    "choices": [
      "A. Emre Can",
      "B. Roberto Firmino",
      "C. Philippe Coutinho",
      "D. No players"
    ],
    "answer": "B",
    "type": "future",
    "question_level": "player",
    "related_event_index": [
      3
    ],
    "current_event_index": 2,
    "index": 8,
    "event_type": "goal"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many corners have occurred so far in the first half up to the 4:22 mark?",
    "choices": [
      "A. 0",
      "B. 1",
      "C. 2",
      "D. 3"
    ],
    "answer": "B",
    "type": "past",
    "question_level": "match",
    "related_event_index": [
      0
    ],
    "current_event_index": 0,
    "index": 0,
    "event_type": "corner"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which team has taken more corners in the first half up to the 4:22 mark?",
    "choices": [
      "A. Liverpool",
      "B. Opponent",
      "C. Both teams have taken equal corners",
      "D. No corners taken yet"
    ],
    "answer": "A",
    "type": "past",
    "question_level": "team",
    "related_event_index": [
      0
    ],
    "current_event_index": 0,
    "index": 1,
    "event_type": "corner"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which player took the first corner in the first half up to the 4:22 mark?",
    "choices": [
      "A. Mohamed Salah",
      "B. Philippe Coutinho",
      "C. Virgil van Dijk",
      "D. No corners taken yet"
    ],
    "answer": "A",
    "type": "past",
    "question_level": "player",
    "related_event_index": [
      0
    ],
    "current_event_index": 0,
    "index": 2,
    "event_type": "corner"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many total corners occurred in the first half?",
    "choices": [
      "A. 0",
      "B. 1",
      "C. 2",
      "D. 3"
    ],
    "answer": "C",
    "type": "half",
    "question_level": "match",
    "related_event_index": [
      0,
      1
    ],
    "current_event_index": null,
    "index": 3,
    "event_type": "corner"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which team had the most corners in the first half?",
    "choices": [
      "A. Liverpool",
      "B. Opponent",
      "C. Both teams had equal corners",
      "D. No corners taken"
    ],
    "answer": "A",
    "type": "half",
    "question_level": "team",
    "related_event_index": [
      0,
      1
    ],
    "current_event_index": null,
    "index": 4,
    "event_type": "corner"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which player was involved in the most corners in the first half?",
    "choices": [
      "A. Mohamed Salah",
      "B. Philippe Coutinho",
      "C. Both players were involved equally",
      "D. No corners taken"
    ],
    "answer": "C",
    "type": "half",
    "question_level": "player",
    "related_event_index": [
      0,
      1
    ],
    "current_event_index": null,
    "index": 5,
    "event_type": "corner"
  },
  {
    "question": "Will there be more corners in the first half after the 4:22 mark?",
    "choices": [
      "A. Yes",
      "B. No"
    ],
    "answer": "A",
    "type": "future",
    "question_level": "match",
    "related_event_index": [
      1
    ],
    "current_event_index": 0,
    "index": 6,
    "event_type": "corner"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which team is more likely to get the next corner after the 4:22 mark?",
    "choices": [
      "A. Liverpool",
      "B. Opponent"
    ],
    "answer": "A",
    "type": "future",
    "question_level": "team",
    "related_event_index": [
      1
    ],
    "current_event_index": 0,
    "index": 7,
    "event_type": "corner"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which player is most likely to be involved in the next corner after the 4:22 mark?",
    "choices": [
      "A. Mohamed Salah",
      "B. Philippe Coutinho",
      "C. Virgil van Dijk",
      "D. None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "B",
    "type": "future",
    "question_level": "player",
    "related_event_index": [
      1
    ],
    "current_event_index": 0,
    "index": 8,
    "event_type": "corner"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many corners have occurred so far in the first half up to the 29:40 mark?",
    "choices": [
      "A. 0",
      "B. 1",
      "C. 2",
      "D. 3"
    ],
    "answer": "C",
    "type": "past",
    "question_level": "match",
    "related_event_index": [
      0,
      1
    ],
    "current_event_index": 1,
    "index": 9,
    "event_type": "corner"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which team has taken more corners in the first half up to the 29:40 mark?",
    "choices": [
      "A. Liverpool",
      "B. Opponent",
      "C. Both teams have taken equal corners",
      "D. No corners taken yet"
    ],
    "answer": "A",
    "type": "past",
    "question_level": "team",
    "related_event_index": [
      0,
      1
    ],
    "current_event_index": 1,
    "index": 10,
    "event_type": "corner"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which players have taken corners in the first half up to the 29:40 mark?",
    "choices": [
      "A. Mohamed Salah",
      "B. Philippe Coutinho",
      "C. Both A and B",
      "D. None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "C",
    "type": "past",
    "question_level": "player",
    "related_event_index": [
      0,
      1
    ],
    "current_event_index": 1,
    "index": 11,
    "event_type": "corner"
  },
  {
    "question": "Will there be more corners in the first half after the 29:40 mark?",
    "choices": [
      "A. Yes",
      "B. No"
    ],
    "answer": "B",
    "type": "future",
    "question_level": "match",
    "related_event_index": [],
    "current_event_index": 1,
    "index": 12,
    "event_type": "corner"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which team is more likely to get the next corner after the 29:40 mark?",
    "choices": [
      "A. Liverpool",
      "B. Opponent",
      "C. Neither",
      "D. Both"
    ],
    "answer": "C",
    "type": "future",
    "question_level": "team",
    "related_event_index": [],
    "current_event_index": 1,
    "index": 13,
    "event_type": "corner"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which player is most likely to be involved in the next corner after the 29:40 mark?",
    "choices": [
      "A. Mohamed Salah",
      "B. Philippe Coutinho",
      "C. Virgil van Dijk",
      "D. None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "D",
    "type": "future",
    "question_level": "player",
    "related_event_index": [],
    "current_event_index": 1,
    "index": 14,
    "event_type": "corner"
  }
]